// Answers are 0-3 (i.e. 1-4) per Java
var questions = [
    {
        question: "How long was the 100 Years War between England and France?",
        options: ["98 years", "100 years", "149 years", "114 years"],
        answer: "114 years"
    },
    {
        question: "The American War for Independence began in 1776, but when did America offically win the war?",
        options: ["1776", "1781", "1783", "1789"],
        answer: "1783"
    },    
    {
        question: "Which war was also know as The Great War",
        options: ["World War 1", "World War 2", "The American Civil War", "The Cold War"],
        answer: "World War 1"
    },    
    {
        question: "When Christopher Columbus discovered the New World, the three ships were named the Nina, the Pinta, and the ...",
        options: ["Santa Monica", "Santa Maria", "Forida", "Sangria"],
        answer: "Santa Maria"
    },    
    {
        question: "The Library of Alexander was located in which ancint civilization?",
        options: ["Rome", "Egypt", "Athens", "Sparta"],
        answer: "Egypt"
    },    
    {
        question: "Which Historical Empire is known to be the biggest in size?",
        options: ["Mongol", "Russian", "Qing", "British"],
        answer: "British"
    },    
    {
        question: "Which country was origially named Siam",
        options: ["Mongol", "Cambodia", "Laos", "Thialand"],
        answer: "Thialand"
    },    
    {
        question: "Which country was origially named Ceylon",
        options: ["Bengal", "Cambodia", "Sri Lanka", "Thialand"],
        answer: "Sri Lanka"
    },    
    {
        question: "Who were the main economic rivals during the Cold War",
        options: ["Russia and China", "United States and China", "Norway and United States", "Russia and United States"],
        answer: "Russia and United States"
    },    
    {
        question: "Which ancient civilization was located between the rivers Tigris and Euphrates?",
        options: ["Indus Valley", "Mesopotamia", "Incan", "Mayan"],
        answer: "Mesopotamia"
    },
];